<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Theology on imjeremy</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/theology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Theology on imjeremy</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/theology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My favourite Catholic Resources</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/theology/my-favourite-catholic-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/theology/my-favourite-catholic-resources/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://open.spotify.com/show/1CBXBk2WSTYUbtAtaOBF26?si=CWLx60yfSUO4LqXeKc8Uiw&#34;&gt;Catholic Daily Reflections&lt;/a&gt;  - This is an awesome 5 minute audio, that includes a bible reading, a reflection, a challenge for you and concludes with prayer. So much Gold here.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Anything Trent Horn. But&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why you should believe</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/theology/why-you-should-believe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/theology/why-you-should-believe/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For me, this has to be one of, if not &lt;strong&gt;the most important question&lt;/strong&gt; someone can ever ask. We&amp;rsquo;re talking not just about how we came to be, but also why we were made and whether there&amp;rsquo;s life after death. For many, this will never be a priority to ponder—not unless death comes knocking on their door.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My personal reasoning for why I believe has changed progressively over the years and has evolved in many ways. I started as a cradle Catholic and was taught to believe at a very young age. However, like a majority of cradle Catholics, my faith was very watered down. I remember going to a YFC (Youth for Christ) camp and on Day 1, telling everyone that I was just there for the girls. What an embarrassment! However, from that camp I saw that being Christian could be &amp;lsquo;cool&amp;rsquo;. I saw Christians break dancing, rapping, hip-hopping, and singing praise and worship songs. Sure, it may have been a bit superficial, but it was a good start in realizing that being Christian didn&amp;rsquo;t have to mean being boring.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
