<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Theology on imjeremy</title>
    <link>http://localhost:63444/theology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Theology on imjeremy</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:63444/theology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My favourite Catholic Resources</title>
      <link>http://localhost:63444/theology/my-favourite-catholic-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:63444/theology/my-favourite-catholic-resources/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://open.spotify.com/show/1CBXBk2WSTYUbtAtaOBF26?si=CWLx60yfSUO4LqXeKc8Uiw&#34;&gt;Catholic Daily Reflections&lt;/a&gt;  - This is an awesome 5 minute audio, that includes a bible reading, a reflection, a challenge for you and concludes with prayer. So much Gold here.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Anything Trent Horn. But&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why you should believe</title>
      <link>http://localhost:63444/theology/why-you-should-believe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:63444/theology/why-you-should-believe/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For me, this has to be one of, if not the most important question someone can ever ask. We&amp;rsquo;re talking not just about how we came to be, but also why we were made and if there&amp;rsquo;s a life after death. For many, this will never be a priority to ponder, not unless death comes knocking on their doors.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My personal reasoning as to why I believe has changed progressively over the years and has evolved in many ways. I started as a cradle Catholic, so I was taught to believe at a very young age. However, like a majority of cradle Catholics, my faith was very watered down. I remember going to an YFC (Youth for Christ) camp and on Day-1, telling everyone that I was just there for the girls. What an embarrassment. However, from that camp I saw that being Christian could be &amp;lsquo;cool&amp;rsquo;. I saw Christians Break dancing, rapping, hip hopping, and also singing to Praise and Worship. Sure, it may have been a bit superficial, but it was a good start in knowing that Christians doesnt need to mean boring. As life progressed, I exposed myself to more Catholic circles. Slowly my faith grew through friendships, music, testimonials, keynote speakers, Catholic radio, and podcasts. I started to connected dots in faith and understanding. I began to understand truths about my faith and how it would influence my everyday life. My life started to feel so free and is constantly filled with joy. My faith has taught me how to love my friends, family, and spouse in ways I would never have found otherwise.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
