<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>imjeremy</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on imjeremy</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 12:04:16 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>3D Prints</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/3d-printing/3dprints/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 12:04:16 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/3d-printing/3dprints/</guid>
      <description>Images can be added to posts using Markdown syntax:&#xA;![Sample image](workday.jpg) Which looks like this:&#xA;You can also use Hugo&amp;rsquo;s built-in figure shortcode. This lets you add a caption, and looks like this:&#xA;Black and white work day photo. Posts with images are great at capturing attention and showcasing your work. Why not try it today?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Adobo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/kitchen/why-i-believe-in-a-god/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 12:04:16 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/kitchen/why-i-believe-in-a-god/</guid>
      <description>Um, no need to cook. Just go find a nice filipino family and open their fridge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/prayers/glorious-mysteries-wednesday-_-sunday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/prayers/glorious-mysteries-wednesday-_-sunday/</guid>
      <description>1. The Resurrection of Jesus Christ&#xD;2. The Ascension of Jesus to Heaven&#xD;3. The Descent of the Holy Ghost&#xD;4. The Assumption of Mary into Heaven&#xD;5. Mary is Crowned as Queen of Heaven and Earth&#xD;1st Glorious Mystery: The Resurrection of Jesus Christ&#xD;At dawn of the first day of the week, I was with John and Peter. I was in my room alone: John and Peter were in the next room.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/prayers/how-to-pray-the-rosary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/prayers/how-to-pray-the-rosary/</guid>
      <description>How to pray the Rosary&#xD;Begin by holding the crucifix, saying &amp;ldquo;In the Name of the Father and of the Son and of the Holy Spirit,&amp;rdquo; (making the sign of the Cross while doing that), then say the Apostles Creed. In the name of the Father of the Son and of the Holy Spirit. Amen&#xA;The Apostles&amp;rsquo; Creed: I believe in God the Father Almighty, Creator of heaven and earth; and in Jesus Christ, His only Son, our Lord; Who was conceived by the Holy Ghost, born of the Virgin Mary, suffered under Pontius Pilate, was crucified, died and was buried.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/prayers/joyful-mysteries-monday-_-saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/prayers/joyful-mysteries-monday-_-saturday/</guid>
      <description>1. The Annunciation of the Lord to Mary&#xD;2. The Visitation of Mary to Elizabeth&#xD;3. The Nativity of our Lord Jesus Christ&#xD;4. The Presentation of our Lord&#xD;5. Finding Jesus in the Temple at age 12 1st Joyful Mystery: The Annunciation of the Lord to Mary&#xD;I was in prayer: it was evening. I was praying towards Jerusalem because my people prayed three times a day, morning, noon, and evening facing Jerusalem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/prayers/luminous-mysteries-thursday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/prayers/luminous-mysteries-thursday/</guid>
      <description>1. The Baptism in the Jordan&#xD;2. The Wedding at Cana&#xD;3. The Proclamation of the Kingdom&#xD;4. The Transfiguration&#xD;5. The Institution of the Eucharist&#xD;1. The Baptism in the Jordan&#xD;John is baptizing in the Jordan proclaiming a baptism of repentance. &amp;ldquo;I am the voice of one crying in the desert, make straight the way of the Lord.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;One mightier than I is coming after me.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;I have baptized you with water, He will baptize you with the Holy Spirit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/prayers/sorrowful-mysteries-tuesday-_-friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/prayers/sorrowful-mysteries-tuesday-_-friday/</guid>
      <description>1. The Agony of Jesus in the Garden&#xD;2. The Scourging at the Pillar&#xD;3. Jesus is Crowned with Thorns&#xD;4. Jesus Carried the Cross&#xD;5. The Crucifixion of our Lord&#xD;1st Sorrowful Mystery: The Agony of Jesus in the Garden&#xD;My Son came with His apostles to the mount of Olives. There was a garden there that He frequently went to pray: He felt a sadness; a deep, deep sadness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Angelus</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/prayers/angelus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/prayers/angelus/</guid>
      <description>The Angelus has been traditionally said three times daily, at 6 am, noon and 6 pm&#xA;V. The Angel of the Lord declared unto Mary, R. And she conceived of the Holy Spirit.&#xA;Hail Mary, etc&amp;hellip;&#xA;V. Behold the handmaid of the Lord. R. Be it done unto me according to Your Word.&#xA;Hail Mary, etc&amp;hellip;&#xA;V. And the Word was made flesh, (all bow or genuflect as these words are spoken) R.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apostles Creed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/prayers/apostles-creed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/prayers/apostles-creed/</guid>
      <description>I believe in God, the Father Almighty, Creator of Heaven and earth; and in Jesus Christ, His only Son, Our Lord, Who was conceived by the Holy Ghost, born of the Virgin Mary, suffered under Pontius Pilate, was crucified; died, and was buried. He descended into Hell; the third day He arose again from the dead; He ascended into Heaven, sitteth at the right hand of God, the Father Almighty; from thence He shall come to judge the living and the dead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confiteor</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/prayers/confiteor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/prayers/confiteor/</guid>
      <description>I confess to almighty God and to you, my brothers and sisters, that I have greatly sinned in my thoughts and in my words, in what I have done, and in what I have failed to do; through my fault, through my fault, through my most grievous fault; therefore I ask blessed Mary ever-Virgin, all the Angels and Saints, and you, my brothers and sisters, to pray for me to the Lord our God.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gloria</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/prayers/gloria/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/prayers/gloria/</guid>
      <description>Glory to God in the highest, and peace to God&amp;rsquo;s people on earth. Lord God, heavenly King, almighty God and Father, we worship you, we give you thanks; we praise you for your glory. Lord Jesus Christ, only Son of the Father, Lord God, Lamb of God, you take away the sin of the world: have mercy on us; you are seated at the right hand of the Father: receive our prayer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hail Holy Queen</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/prayers/hail-holy-queen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/prayers/hail-holy-queen/</guid>
      <description>Hail, holy Queen, Mother of Mercy! our life, our sweetness, and our hope! To thee do we cry, poor banished children of Eve; to thee do we send up our sighs, mourning and weeping in this valley, of tears. Turn, then, most gracious Advocate, thine eyes of mercy toward us; and after this our exile show unto us the blessed fruit of thy womb, Jesus; O clement, O loving, O sweet Virgin Mary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hi, I&#39;m Jeremy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/home/</guid>
      <description>Disciple. Husband. Pilgrim.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Litany of Humlity</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/prayers/litany-of-humlity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/prayers/litany-of-humlity/</guid>
      <description>The first set of petitions in the Litany of Humility requests our deliverance from desiring validation from man instead of God.&#xA;O Jesus! meek and humble of heart, Hear me. Response for the following: Deliver me, Jesus. From the desire of being esteemed … From the desire of being loved … From the desire of being extolled … From the desire of being honored … From the desire of being praised … From the desire of being preferred to others… From the desire of being consulted … From the desire of being approved … The second set of petitions address our fears that are related to pride.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memorare</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/prayers/memorare/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/prayers/memorare/</guid>
      <description>Remember O Most Gracious Virgin Mary, that never was it known that anyone who fled unto Thy protection, implored Thy help or sought Thine intercession, was left unaided by Thee. Inspired by this confidence I fly onto Thee, O Virgin of virgins, my Mother. To Thee I come, before Thee I stand, sinful and sorrowful. Do not, O Mother of the Word Incarnate, despise my petitions but, in Thy clemency, hear and answer me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Night Prayers to Say at Bedtime</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/prayers/7-calming-night-prayers-to-say-at-bedtime/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/prayers/7-calming-night-prayers-to-say-at-bedtime/</guid>
      <description>Taken directly from Jeannie Myers - https://www.biblestudytools.com/bible-study/topical-studies/calming-prayers-to-say-before-bed.html&#xA;Bedtime prayer can be a meaningful way to spend time with God every evening, talking over your day, sharing your concerns with Him, and thanking Him for His love and care. But why should we take time to pray before bed each night?&#xA;Praying as you fall asleep gives you the chance to look back over the day and thank God for His help and His blessings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prayer to the Angels of God</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/prayers/prayer-to-the-angels-of-god/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/prayers/prayer-to-the-angels-of-god/</guid>
      <description>Guardian Angel&#xD;Angel of God, my Guardian dear, to whom His love commits me here, ever this day (or night) be at my side, to light and guard, to rule and guide. Amen. A Mother&amp;rsquo;s Prayer to the Guardian Angels of her children I humbly salute you, O you faithful, heavenly Friends of my children! I give you heartfelt thanks for all the love and goodness you show them. At some future day I shall, with thanks more worthy than I can now give, repay your care for them, and before the whole heavenly court acknowledge their indebtedness to your guidance and protection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Salve Regina</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/prayers/salve-regina/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/prayers/salve-regina/</guid>
      <description>Latin&#xD;Salve, Regina, mater misericordiae: Vita, dulcedo, et spes nostra, salve. Ad te clamamus, exsules, filii Hevae. Ad te suspiramus, gementes et flentes In hac lacrimarum valle. Eia ergo, Advocata nostra, Illos tuos misericordes oculos Ad nos converte. Et Jesum, benedictum fructum ventris tui, nobis, post hoc exsilium ostende. O clemens! O pia! O dulcis Virgo Maria!&#xA;English&#xD;Hail, holy Queen, mother of mercy, Our life, our sweetness, and our hope.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
